module.exports = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'The volume 2014 of a given mass of gas is general same with all ideal gases, this is state by who?',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Avagadro', 'Charles', 'Boyles', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Avagadro'
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What is the name of the scientic who discovered grivitaional force',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Newton', 'Uche', 'Harwken', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Newton'
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is the dimension of force8 i am tired of typeing ',
        options: ['MLT11', 'MLT22', 'MLT333', 'ML4T4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'MLT11'
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Give another name of projectile motion',
        options: ['Tragetory', 'Translational', 'Rotational', 'Rocket Motion', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Tragetory'
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is quntum mechincis all about',
        options: ['Speed above that of light', 'very light particle', 'relativity', 'none', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'very light particle'
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What is the name of the first space shutle to first land safely on the moon',
        options: ['NASA', 'Space X', 'None', 'All', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'None'
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is the numerical value for the moons grivitaional constant if a pendulum clock is 2.5  time faster on the moon',
        options: ['10', '9.6', '1.6', '4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '1.6'
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What is the number of side owned by a pentagon',
        options: ['1', '2', '4', '5', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'The volume of a given mass of gas is general same with all ideal gases, this is state by who?',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Avagadro', 'Charles', 'Boyles', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Avagadro'
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'What is the name of the scientic who discovered grivitaional force',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Newton', 'Uche', 'Harwken', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Newton'
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What is the dimension of force8 i am tired of typeing ',
        options: ['MLT11', 'MLT22', 'MLT333', 'ML4T4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'MLT11'
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'Give another name of projectile motion',
        options: ['Tragetory', 'Translational', 'Rotational', 'Rocket Motion', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Tragetory'
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'What is quntum mechincis all about',
        options: ['Speed above that of light', 'very light particle', 'relativity', 'none', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'very light particle'
    },
    {
        id: 16,
        question: 'What is the name of the first space shutle to first land safely on the moon',
        options: ['NASA', 'Space X', 'None', 'All', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'None'
    },
    {
        id: 17,
        question: 'What is the numerical value for the moons grivitaional constant if a pendulum clock is 2.5  time faster on the moon',
        options: ['10', '9.6', '1.6', '4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '1.6'
    },
    {
        id: 18,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 19,
        question: 'What is the number of side owned by a pentagon',
        options: ['1', '2', '4', '5', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        id: 20,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 21,
        question: 'The volume of a given mass of gas is general same with all ideal gases, this is state by who?',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Avagadro', 'Charles', 'Boyles', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Avagadro'
    },
    {
        id: 22,
        question: 'What is the name of the scientic who discovered grivitaional force',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Newton', 'Uche', 'Harwken', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Newton'
    },
    {
        id: 23,
        question: 'What is the dimension of force8 i am tired of typeing ',
        options: ['MLT11', 'MLT22', 'MLT333', 'ML4T4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'MLT11'
    },
    {
        id: 24,
        question: 'Give another name of projectile motion',
        options: ['Tragetory', 'Translational', 'Rotational', 'Rocket Motion', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Tragetory'
    },
    {
        id: 25,
        question: 'What is quntum mechincis all about',
        options: ['Speed above that of light', 'very light particle', 'relativity', 'none', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'very light particle'
    },
    {
        id: 26,
        question: 'What is the name of the first space shutle to first land safely on the moon',
        options: ['NASA', 'Space X', 'None', 'All', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'None'
    },
    {
        id: 27,
        question: 'What is the numerical value for the moons grivitaional constant if a pendulum clock is 2.5  time faster on the moon',
        options: ['10', '9.6', '1.6', '4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '1.6'
    },
    {
        id: 28,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 29,
        question: 'What is the number of side owned by a pentagon',
        options: ['1', '2', '4', '5', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        id: 30,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 31,
        question: 'The volume of a given mass of gas is general same with all ideal gases, this is state by who?',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Avagadro', 'Charles', 'Boyles', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Avagadro'
    },
    {
        id: 32,
        question: 'What is the name of the scientic who discovered grivitaional force',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Newton', 'Uche', 'Harwken', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Newton'
    },
    {
        id: 33,
        question: 'What is the dimension of force8 i am tired of typeing ',
        options: ['MLT11', 'MLT22', 'MLT333', 'ML4T4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'MLT11'
    },
    {
        id: 34,
        question: 'Give another name of projectile motion',
        options: ['Tragetory', 'Translational', 'Rotational', 'Rocket Motion', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Tragetory'
    },
    {
        id: 35,
        question: 'What is quntum mechincis all about',
        options: ['Speed above that of light', 'very light particle', 'relativity', 'none', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'very light particle'
    },
    {
        id: 36,
        question: 'What is the name of the first space shutle to first land safely on the moon',
        options: ['NASA', 'Space X', 'None', 'All', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'None'
    },
    {
        id: 37,
        question: 'What is the numerical value for the moons grivitaional constant if a pendulum clock is 2.5  time faster on the moon',
        options: ['10', '9.6', '1.6', '4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '1.6'
    },
    {
        id: 38,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 39,
        question: 'What is the number of side owned by a pentagon',
        options: ['1', '2', '4', '5', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        id: 40,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 41,
        question: 'The volume of a given mass of gas is general same with all ideal gases, this is state by who?',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Avagadro', 'Charles', 'Boyles', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Avagadro'
    },
    {
        id: 42,
        question: 'What is the name of the scientic who discovered grivitaional force',
        options: ['Enstein', 'Newton', 'Uche', 'Harwken', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Newton'
    },
    {
        id: 43,
        question: 'What is the dimension of force8 i am tired of typeing ',
        options: ['MLT11', 'MLT22', 'MLT333', 'ML4T4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'MLT11'
    },
    {
        id: 44,
        question: 'Give another name of projectile motion',
        options: ['Tragetory', 'Translational', 'Rotational', 'Rocket Motion', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'Tragetory'
    },
    {
        id: 45,
        question: 'What is quntum mechincis all about',
        options: ['Speed above that of light', 'very light particle', 'relativity', 'none', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'very light particle'
    },
    {
        id: 46,
        question: 'What is the name of the first space shutle to first land safely on the moon',
        options: ['NASA', 'Space X', 'None', 'All', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'None'
    },
    {
        id: 47,
        question: 'What is the numerical value for the moons grivitaional constant if a pendulum clock is 2.5  time faster on the moon',
        options: ['10', '9.6', '1.6', '4', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '1.6'
    },
    {
        id: 48,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
    {
        id: 49,
        question: 'What is the number of side owned by a pentagon',
        options: ['1', '2', '4', '5', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: '5'
    },
    {
        id: 50,
        question: 'What is your stand on the saying the time is demensionless',
        options: ['yes, i agree', 'no it is not', 'Maybe', 'i dont know', 'you should not be asking me this'],
        answer: 'yes, i agree'
    },
]